It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like the wind.
Jump high.
Yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going on the stage.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
Know what you're making, my dream time to.
Don't you feel it, I
really don't know what is.
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
The greater no day I know you.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wild, girl.
I'm no afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can't do it, so can you only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like the wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you cannot achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, rolling.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your wife that I
want, but you're where it was.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you're gonna kick your best.
Let's keep on going, I'm not dead.
You make my day every day.
Doth Flamingo!
Look at you two, huddled
together in your little hole.
Should I take those
handcuffs off for you long?
Or should I cut your
wrists along with them?
I thought you were at the palace.
What are you doing down here?
I came to rescue you, of course.
You clearly need help if you're
falling for traps like this.
I'll put you out of your misery.
Be careful!
Bullet string.
get the ball get away
no sense of self-preservation
don't die Lucy it's okay what
a joke look at you any clown
could kill you in this sorry state
you've riled up quite an army of idiots
out there thinking they can take my head
you are quite adept at bringing
people to your side no matter
how foolish it may seem i've
admired that quality of yours
since i saw it on display during
the battle at marineford but
now i see you're just some fool
whose luck has finally run out
Why did you side with this idiot, Law?
When you were young, I thought you
showed a great deal of promise.
Even as a child, you were
more cunning than this.
And more ruthless.
Am I wrong?
I'm so disappointed.
Who made you into such a miserable
little coward? That's enough!
You listen!
I'm not gonna be like you!
Because I...
I've been saved!
By my dear brother Corazon, you mean?
You're worse than a coward.
You're useless.
You made a choice, not only to die in
vain, but to do it alongside this imbecile.
Don't you dare!
Keep your hands off Strahan!
Or you'll be sorry!
It's not the real thing it's just
a clone oh a puppet made of string
Thank you guys. Are you okay?
Glad we came.
Anyway, let's get him out of
that water already, right?
Ugh.
You saved me.
Thank you.
Oh, it was nothing. One question.
Did we win?
He's just legs now.
That's the guy we were supposed
to fight at the palace, right?
Moron.
I just told you.
It's only his puppet.
Though I don't know why he bothered
to send one all the way here.
Does he want to taunt us that badly?
That reminds me.
That Kelly Funk guy from
before, he tricked us.
Everything that bastard said was a lie.
Kid's a real sucker.
He walks straight into that one.
After we learned what he was
plotting, we knew we had to stop him.
Drahat needs our help!
Get up, Abdullah!
Kelly's a famous assassin, and he
cut him down in a split second.
Aw, man, that's not fair.
Mingo did rescue me. Treffy is right.
He's laughing at us.
How's Cabbage doing?
Is he beating us?
Yeah, we're falling way behind.
It's been a while.
everyone might be on the second
level ah we gotta get to the
sunflower field I needed that shortcut
hurry back to the entrance what
all those losers made it
up to the second level
already that's crazy our We're
on the leads, I'll lose ease.
I don't see Straw Hat
or his crew out there.
Let's start picking him off, one by one.
Elephant gun, let's go!
What is that? Oh, crap!
It's coming our way!
You don't even know what it is.
You have no right to be scared.
You keep fighting.
Don't lose sight of the enemy.
He made a shortcut with his face!
Hey, guys!
You take care of Moosey for me, okay?
Yes, sir!
Ya-ho-ho!
I'm enjoying this chaos!
Change how all the others are
headed to the third level!
Stop them! Ah! What happened?
That hole...
it came out of nowhere!
A hand?
That's right!
Get ready!
Is that law I see?
What's the hold-up? Move it! All right!
I'm coming for you, Mingo!
They're too small!
Oh...
Yep!
Here, hold on to these ropes.
We're too heavy.
There's no way they can carry us.
Let's leave the bugs and run instead.
Yep, yep.
That sounds much better.
Now, I'll tell you how this works.
You aren't listening, are ya?
This is the Tantata Airline
Special Jumping Service.
Big people are too heavy to
fly on their backs, after all.
Oh, yeah, you think?
There's no more time to explain!
Get a running start and take off! Huh?
We're not flying, we're falling!
Leo, please don't kill our friends!
Hey, are you alright?
If I fall to my death,
I'm gonna hurt you, rants!
This is like flying.
If nothing else, we can
make you all fall slowly.
Those buildings are
getting closer and closer!
It's fine, relax!
But how is this relaxing?
I'm gonna crash!
Try to aim for a rooftop!
Huh? A rooftop?
Yeah, that's it.
Land softly and keep running.
Now go! Jump!
I'm flying!
If you keep kicking off the
rooftops, you can stay in the air!
Very clever.
I think I'm catching on.
Wow, you're really soaring!
Guys, I feel like a balloon!
Someone still might
attack us, so watch out!
Otherwise, just head for the
fourth level of the big plateau!
Roger that. Roger that. Got it!
We're here!
I've got a plan that'll get
the door to the factory open!
Huh? Really?
Definitely!
Just keep fighting Senor for now!
We need time to pull this off!
Easy peasy!
You can count on me!
Bastard, how dare you step on my sword!
Did I? Too bad.
This is one hell of a fight!
Hey, hey, Doofy, did you send
Strain Joker off somewhere?
Yeah, I was gonna deliver something,
but I guess he doesn't need it.
While we're sitting here waiting, do you
remember the day when Law first showed up?
all those years ago.
He was crazy.
Had a wild look in his eyes.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Reminded me of myself when I
was that age, to be honest.
I thought in 10 years, this hateful little
monster will make a fine right-hand man.
but now it looks like i'll be
killing him instead, such a pity.
we have an intruder—don't touch him—he
has explosives strapped to his body.
hey, who
the hell is this kid?
let me join your pirate crew—i
want to destroy everything that.
destroy everything that
I see.
People, towns.
I want to bring this
whole world to the ground.
You know, I'm from
Vlevens, but I came here
from the White Town.
It won't be long before
I'm dead. I'm dead!
Minko!
How strange to be feeling
sentimental at a time like this.
I don't suppose you're going to tell
me you killed Straw Hat like I asked.
Why did you send Deliger to take me out?
Was he really doing that
on your order like he said?
Come on.
It's obvious.
Is there any hope for me to join you?
You really want me to
spell it out for you?
All right.
Your purpose has never been the
same as mine, even from the start.
For example, you always
wanted to be a pirate, right?
Me, not so much.
The methods didn't matter.
For what?
For the only thing I care about.
Destroying this world.
Get out of my way, child!
I'm in quite the hurry.
Really?
You think I'm just a child?
You may not be the beheader
Doesn't that sound scary?
He's fast So how many hits have
you taken? A hundred? A thousand?
If I recall, you were a war executioner
right I love executions, too! You know...
He's a kicker!
Oh, what a shame.
It's over already.
Damn it.
The executives are here.
Looks like I'll be reaching the
third level before anyone else.
What are these strange bulbous masses?
Careful, it's not safe there.
Mine, pop.
Grandpa! Papa!
I'm on my way! Da-ee!
Floaty-floaty!
Ten-ton lights!
Yeah, suck on that!
The family executives are
going to brutalize you!
Sucker!
You losers aren't going anywhere now!
I got you!
Arms morphosis!
Revolver leg!
Okay! Go!
Bring the rope, quick! And treat him!
He's been shot!
Time to put out the fire. Ready? Yeah!
I'm sorry. Thank you.
You saved me.
I was about to kill my own family.
I set the town on fire.
I'm sorry.
I cut up my own best friend. So did I.
It was awful.
Nobody blames you for this.
You're a victim.
We all know this is Doflamingo's work.
We gotta bring an end to
this sadistic game somehow.
Hey!
I was looking around and found King Rick!
And he's got that five-star
god Usopp guy with him!
All right, let's do it.
Right, but we're only capturing them.
Understand?
Uh-huh.
There's been enough killing today.
Let's put an end to this.
Move in quick, then take King Rick
and god Usopp as hostages. Yeah!
Then we can use them to lure in
the others with star bounties.
Yeah!
Tell everyone you can!
We'll all come together at
the Old King's Plateau. Yeah!
What are you lazy bugs doing?
Did you idiots knock over this SAD tank?
It's spilling everywhere.
Come on, pick it up.
Are you OK?
It wasn't us.
There was an earthquake out of the blue,
and then before we knew
it, the tank fell flat!
We promise!
Did something cause that earthquake?
Shut your hole!
You don't need to worry about that stuff!
But...
Come on, guys!
You want to cure Princess
Monterey's illness or not?
What if she dies, huh?
Of course we want to save her!
How is she?
We haven't heard in a while!
I'm sorry to say that the princess
isn't getting any better at all!
Not at all!
Let us see the princess just once.
You're such a little nuisance.
Shut up and get to work.
Those smiles aren't
going to make themselves,
so stop gawking or you're
all going to get the whip.
Are you listening to me?
Am I not speaking loud
enough, you dimwits?
Quit zoning out!
What's wrong with you?!
Those letters, they're...
The pink bees!
Beyond!
And now, wake up!
Good!
They noticed us, Beyond!
Roger that!
Okay, team, the next message!
Uh, we got fooled?
I don't understand.
If you won't listen, I'm gonna
make the whip do the talking!
Fooled about the princess?
Fooled about her illness?
Doflamingo has been lying
to keep us trapped here?
All right, I got no choice
but to beat it into you.
I don't know what's going on, but
there's one thing I'm sure of.
My friends wouldn't lie!
Shut up, underlings!
Oh, it's Drawhead!
So Flamingo's up at the
top of this place, right?
Cabbage, you try to get in my way again!
Not this time.
Hop on.
Not my first choice, but I've
decided to give you a ride.
Are you serious?
You need to get to Doflamingo
quickly, don't you?
All right!
Let's get going! Ride!
What a small hint of gratitude!
Kill you!
Just make the horse go!
Don't tell me what to do!
Let's go, Farul.
Listen, if the executives catch
us, we'll be stuck here for ages.
I'll cut through the wall and make a path.
You knock the enemies out of our way.
Got it!
We'll push through to the
third level in one shot.
Hey!
When the hell did we pick
up an extra passenger?
Oh, hey, soldier.
What are you doing on my horse?
Riding.
I followed Luffyland's trail
and it brought me here.
Wait! Get off! Lucky break.
I was looking for you.
I don't care if you're friends.
Four's too many.
We're gonna meet up with
Rebecca after we go up a level.
Rebecca's in enemy territory?
You didn't stop her?
Don't ignore me!
She's headed up to the sunflower
field to deliver a key to me.
But she's on the wanted list.
What if somebody captures her?
Don't worry.
My friends are there to protect her.
Listen!
My elegant steed can't maintain its
elegance with four people on its back!
I was more comfortable riding on the bull.
By the way, Pops, why did you
take off in such a hurry before?
My goal in this is the same as yours.
I must liberate this kingdom and beat
O 'Flamingo as swiftly as possible.
But there's one more thing.
A personal matter that I must settle.
A top executive that I must
kill with my own two hands.
that's fine but don't die trying okay
of course not i won't be defeated
with my true body okay then not okay
get off why don't you get off this
is my horse you're the worst of the
whole worst generation watch where
you're going we're gonna crash look
like i said don't Tell me what to do!
What's that?
We got this.
Go on ahead.
We'll keep them busy, Straw Hat.
Don't worry.
They're a team.
All of a sudden, Ean.
They were one step away from
fighting each other a second ago.
That's cool.
But what's going on here?
You're friends now?
I'm a famous tactician.
And this is war.
I helped them realize we need
each other to grasp victory!
Dagama may be a rat, but
his plan makes sense.
Our best bet is to help Straw Hat win.
So get moving!
You take out the boss.
We'll keep the executives busy.
Get him there, Cavendish.
And make it quick! I see.
So I've been reduced to a chauffeur.
Don't give him an inch! You ready?
Excellent work!
Looks like that stubby
guy is calling the shots.
I'll stomp him out!
Garamon took a big hit!
What?
Hey, let go of me, you jerk!
Keep going, Straw Hats!
Don't look back!
Open fire!
Keep them down there at any cost!
Blade of beauty, sans-t-ex-zu-peri!